Excuse me, sir.
I have a question for you, man.
Is this your G-Wagon?
It is my G-Wagon, yes.
And what do you do for living out
in Scottsdale to be able to afford a G-Wagon?
I'm just in sales.
Are you a business owner?
Oh man, I own a lot of businesses.
How many businesses do you own?
I have about four businesses right
now that are doing eight figures.
What has been the most amount of money
that you've ever made in a single year?
Remember this, revenue is for vanity, profit is for sanity.
We'll do $240 million this year.
Well, we made $160 million last year.
Our goal is to make $250 million this year.
Our goal is to be
at a billion in four years.
And you say, well, how can that happen?
It's simple.
It's a penny a day
doubled every day for 30 days.
And how old were you when you became a millionaire?
That's incredible, man.
Well, you know, I learned how to sell.
That's the secret.
That's my deal.
So if you want to become a millionaire and
become rich in 2024, two things you're going to need.
Number one.
Scottsdale, Arizona is one of the
wealthiest cities in the entire United States.
And today I'm going to be going all over Scottsdale to
talk to some of the wealthiest people in the entire city
to figure out how they created their wealth
and how you can start your path.
To become financially free in 2024.
This video is going to be insane, you guys.
So stay tuned for the end.
With that being said, let's
get this video on the way.
Have you ever been broke before?
Yeah.
Yeah, of course.
Many times.
There was one point.
Listen, for every new level, there's a new devil.
There's been many times even
when I was really doing well,
making tens of millions of
dollars, I was very cash poor.
This is the big misconception
in entrepreneurship is that like,
I made $10 million, I'm balling.
No, I'm not.
I got bills, like big bills.
And there was one point where I had
a $550,000 Amex bill due the next day.
I had payroll due the next day.
That was probably like $200 something thousand dollars.
And I had like 300 grand in my account.
And I'm in my underwear in a
9,000 square foot house on the water
by myself at three in the
morning crying in my theater room.
Like just picture this moment.
Like I'm just a mess.
I'm sobbing snot bubbles.
And I'm panicking because I'm like,
what am I going to do?
What would you do?
And then I went back to something
my mentor told me very early on.
And he said, listen, Cody, sales cures everything.
You can hire all the best.
You can figure everything out.
Sell your way out.
This is why sales, persuasion, influence,
the mastering the art of copywriting.
If you can sell well, you can
sell your way out of any challenge.
And that's what I did.
I pulled up my bootstraps.
Winners have a bounce back spirit.
And I just said, you know what?
I'm going to get up tomorrow.
I'm going to rally the team.
We're going to fight like hell.
We're going to come up with a new offer.
We're going to launch it in one day.
I'm going to call the credit
card company and beg for some time.
And I'm going to get at it.
And within about a week and a half,
we sold about $800,000 worth of new product.
And I paid everything off.
And I got myself out of that hole.
You're also a business owner.
Oh, man.
I own a lot of businesses.
How many businesses do you own?
I have about four businesses right
now that are doing eight figures.
What is the blueprint to becoming
a multimillionaire like yourself in today's world?
Yeah, get into real estate.
Write this down.
If you've never thought about
doing it, you're just starting,
look at the single tenant triple net lease game.
All right?
Just look it up.
Start researching.
Because that's a great business to be in.
Wealthy people own a lot.
It'd be like you owning the CVS building
that CVS Pharmacy or Walgreens or something is in,
or a doctor's office is in.
Those high credit rating tenants.
The bigger the deal, the easier it is to do.
This is a big misconception.
I used to think that, man, it's scary to
do a big, huge $5, $10 million commercial deal,
$50 million commercial deal.
The reality is it's easier to do a $50
million commercial deal than a $1 million house flip.
The financing is easier.
The people involved are smarter.
It's just a checklist.
As long as you qualify and pass
the checklist, they give you the money.
You scaled multiple eight-figure businesses.
What was the number one thing
that you implemented throughout your companies
to take them from seven to eight-figure businesses?
Yeah, simple.
I fired myself.
I got the hell out of the way.
I am not the guy.
Like, dude, when I was young,
I was smoking weed, selling drugs, partying.
Like, I wasn't that guy that was class valedictorian.
You know, I'm street smarts.
I'm not really book smarts.
Form this amazing team and get
the hell out of the way.
Money loves speed.
Cut the check.
What is one lesson about business that you would
teach to somebody that they will not learn in school?
It's not going to happen.
Your time frame, it's much more difficult than you think.
And if you're a mental pussy, it's not for you.
Bow out now.
Phenomenal fucking interview, bro.
That was absolutely amazing.
All right, you guys.
We are at a compound out here in Scottsdale, Arizona.
And we're about to
interview a nine-figure blue-collar entrepreneur.
He runs one of the largest
home service-based businesses in the entire country.
We're going to ask him how he was
able to build this empire out here in Scottsdale
and his secret to creating wealth.
Let's go see what he has to say.
What industry did you decide to pursue a career in?
You've heard of Michelin.
Michelin restaurants?
Yes, sir.
I'm actually a dishwasher.
No, I'm kidding.
I have a garage door
company called A1 Garage Door Service.
So blue-collar, home service industry.
Best decision I've ever made.
And how long have you been in the business for?
Two decades.
Good things come to those who wait.
At your company, how much money
are you going to make this year?
We'll do $240 million this year.
You know, we're over 20% of the bottom line.
So remember this.
Revenue is for vanity.
Profit is for sanity.
We run a lot of efficiency.
And because we buy so many garage doors and parts,
you'll go pay this if you're a normal company.
We pay this.
What was the number one book
in your life?
The story goes like this.
2008, I had a CPA
that only worked with 10 clients.
He did me a favor by even being with me.
He goes, are you a reader?
I go, well, I read To Kill a Mockingbird
and then Lord of the Flies.
And he's like, yeah, that was in high school, dude.
He's like, here's the book you should read.
And we hear this book a lot.
The E-Myth Revisited.
Think and Grow Rich by Napoleon Hill.
Dale Carnegie.
But the newest book, good buddy of mine,
he's also a coach of mine,
Dan Martell, Buy Back Your Time.
Like, you could literally buy back your time.
And some people could buy 30 hours a week
and then compound their time.
Elon Musk has done that.
He spends the same amount
of time as we both do.
What is he doing to create efficiencies
and economies of scale so much better?
So studying where your time's going
and how much waste we have,
like there's people on their phone.
I mean, right now,
most people are on their phone probably.
Just scrolling for hours.
I don't think anybody's ever said,
man, I'm really glad I got to go on TikTok
for four hours yesterday.
It changed my life.
So like, if you could buy back your time
and look at efficiency,
I think you could really scale.
Right now, among yourself
and the most highly successful people
that you study and know,
what is that one trait
that they all have in common?
What do you notice consistently
among the most successful people
Well, millionaires have good habits.
Millionaires get up early,
they do the cold plunges.
They get up at 5 a.m.
They're like, ooh, yeah.
They go to church.
They're good family people.
Billionaires are much better at networking.
They don't work as hard.
They know who to call when.
They don't get up at 5 a.m.
They just say, we're having a problem.
I'm calling the best.
And they're not cheap.
They're not trying to negotiate prices.
They just go, I know you're the best.
Best people charge more.
I'm not going to try to negotiate with you.
Here's the results I'm looking for.
I need these results more than I need a deal.
I buy exactly how I want to be bought from.
What was the deepest,
life quote that you've ever heard?
I love this quote.
You guys have probably heard it,
but the magic you're looking for
is in the work you're avoiding.
And I truly believe,
people are like, man, I want a six pack.
Three things.
Three things that I see great people
versus depressed people.
Focus on what you have versus what you don't have.
So many people focus on what they don't have.
You know, you move your fingers,
you wake up, you have energy.
That's more than most people.
Number two, focus on today and the future
versus the past.
And number three, focus on what you can't control
versus what you can't control.
You can't control Israel and Ukraine.
You cannot control the traffic jam.
You can control getting up
out of bed and working out.
You can control that eating something healthy
versus eating that brownie.
And if you focus on those things,
you're going to go further in life.
You got an amazing advice.
Thank you so much for your time.
I appreciate it.
That was my favorite interviews I've ever done.
So my guy's business is going to do
over $200 million this year.
And that was one of the wildest interviews
that I've ever done.
You heard the breakdown,
the difference between millionaires and billionaires.
Millionaires, they may have great habits.
They may know the sauna and the cold plunge,
but billionaires, they are masters at networking
and getting exactly what they want out of the deal
and putting the right people in the right places.
Phenomenal interview.
Let's go get this next one.
So we're on our way
to go get our next interview,
but I want to take a
second to talk to you guys
about something that's told to us time and time again
from the most successful people in the entire world.
Just as it's important to invest in yourself
and your business,
it is equally as important to invest
in your family's future.
And that's why I want to take a second
to talk about the sponsor of today's video,
which is Fabric by Gerber Life.
Fabric by Gerber Life was designed by parents
for parents to make it easy to plan for
and manage your family's financial path.
With a kid's investment account from Fabric,
you can start investing in your child's future today.
While your kids can invest when they're minors,
setting up a kid's investment account
allows you to invest money on their behalf
and it allows their money
to compound and grow over time.
Invested funds can be used for your kid's education
as well as any sports or clubs
or any other extracurricular activities
that they're involved in.
And when they're adults,
they can use these funds to purchase their first home
or to start a business.
And the best part is it's all online.
Setting up an account could take you just five minutes
with as little as $1 a day.
Then you can manage your child's accounts
and monitor their investments right from your phone.
Plus,
you can share your child's unique gifting link
with family and friends.
So instead of them bringing them toys on their birthdays,
which they're going to eventually outgrow,
you can give them the ability
to invest in your kid's future
and they can take that money to start businesses.
So start investing in your child's future today
at meetfabric.com slash hard knocks.
Once again,
that's meetfabric.com slash hard knocks.
And with that being said,
let's go get this next interview.
All right, you guys,
my guy just pulled up in a G-Wagon
out here in Scottsdale, Arizona.
We're going to go up and
see what he was able to do
to be able to afford this.
Let's go see what he has to say.
Excuse me, sir.
Quick question for you, man.
Is this your G-Wagon?
It is my G-Wagon, yes.
And what do you do for living out in Scottsdale
to be able to afford a G-Wagon?
I'm just in sales.
Are you a business owner?
I own a business now.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah?
How long have you been an entrepreneur for?
I started this company late 2018,
so a little over five years ago.
What's been the most amount of money
that you've ever made in a single year?
Company revenues last year,
we did a bit under $34 million.
How old are you now?
I just turned 47.
Old guy.
And how old were you when you became a millionaire?
That's incredible, man.
Well, you know, I learned how to sell.
What was the number one book that changed your life?
I think a really good book for salespeople,
even entrepreneurs or business owners,
a book by Daniel Pink.
It's called The Sellers Human.
I think it came out about 12, 14 years ago.
And it really talks about how buying behaviors
and consumers have radically changed.
And it just opens your eyes up
to get you to kind of like realize
that there's a lot of sales myths out there.
You always hear like people buy from people they like.
Well, that comes from Dale Carnegie's book
in 1936, and it's a great book,
but we're in 2024, not 1936.
Consumers are much different.
Buying behaviors are way different.
They didn't have the internet.
They didn't have social media, right?
I would say that people don't really buy
from people they like.
They buy from people or companies they trust
can get them the best result.
Doesn't necessarily mean they like you,
but they trust you that you can get them
the best result, right?
You love grandma,
but you're not necessarily buying from grandma
if some complete stranger is selling the same thing
and you trust that that stranger,
can get you a better result.
You love grandma,
but you're not buying from grandma.
You're buying from the stranger, right?
You might have a friend that sells hardware
or supplies down the street at a local store,
but you're still buying that stuff from Amazon.
You don't love Amazon.
Maybe you love Jeffrey Bezos.
I don't know, but you trust Amazon
can get you a better result.
Now, I don't mean they should hate you,
but if all things are equal, yeah,
maybe they go with the
person that they like the more,
but very rare is all things equal.
So people buy from people they trust
can get them the best result.
What's the deepest life quote that you ever heard?
From Andy Andrus.
You know, I've ever heard of Andy Andrus.
I saw him at an event like back in 2006,
and he said, God feeds the birds,
but he doesn't drop worms in their nest.
And I'm like, that's so true, man.
Like God gives us all this opportunity.
We have to go out and do something, man.
Like we have agency to choose
what we wanna do in life,
but most people are like, oh, they're all afraid, right?
They never do anything.
So just go out and do something, help people.
I feel like you go out there and you like,
you really have something that you wanna help people.
You're in a G-Wagon right now.
This is a lot of people's dream car.
How can somebody get a G-Wagon in today's world?
The number one thing you
have to have over anything else
is you gotta be freaking committed.
You gotta be fucking committed.
You gotta be a thousand percent committed
with what you wanna do.
Like you can't be flaky.
Like none of my friends who are multimillionaires
and one's a billionaire, none of them are flaky.
Like they're freaking committed, man.
They wake up at a certain time.
They go through a certain, like their day-to-day routine.
Like they are freaking committed.
So like number one, you gotta be committed.
There's no flakiness.
If you wanna be wealthy, there's no flakiness.
Like unless you're like a trust fund kid,
you can't be flaky.
That's number one.
Number two, develop with the right skills.
I'm always gonna come back to the skill level
because your skill level can take you to levels
that most people don't get
because they don't put in the
time to learn the skill level.
And then the third thing I
believe is just building a culture
like building a company where people wanna be around
and they have that same drive.
Like even our salespeople, our operations team,
our marketing team, like they're on the same mission
to change the way sales is perceived in society.
And we share that common goal.
So those three things, most important.
No, I appreciate you, man.
That was great.
This video has been crazy to make you guys,
but I want you to comment down below.
Who's been your favorite interview and why?
We love connecting with you guys.
I wanna know what you all think about this video,
but with that being said,
let's go with this next interview.
We're about to go interview a real legend
out here in Scottsdale, Arizona.
Let's go see what he has to say.
Good man, how about you?
Yeah, I'm following you on Instagram, bro.
What's your name?
Miles.
Miles James, great to meet you, man.
Nice to meet you, bro.
Appreciate that.
For those that don't know,
what industry did you decide to pursue a career in?
What do you do for
living out here in Scottsdale, Arizona?
Well, we own one of the largest coaching companies
in the world, but sales is
what got me where I'm at.
Sales and leadership will get you rich.
If you wanna get rich, you get great at sales,
you become a great leader, you'll dominate everybody.
How much money are you gonna make this year?
What's the most amount of money
that you've ever made in a single year?
Well, we made 160 million last year.
Our goal is to make 250 this year.
Our goal is to be
at a billion in four years.
And you say, well, how can that happen?
It's simple, it's a penny a day
doubled every day for 30 days, okay?
It doesn't always look that way in the beginning,
but it's going in that direction.
It's just like your social media channel
we just showed each other, right?
It took me a year
to get to a million followers.
It took me 90 days
to get to my next million.
You see what I'm saying?
It's a compound effect, baby.
Why was sales your vehicle?
Out of all the industries out there,
all the skills to learn,
why did you master sales above everything else?
Lowest barrier of entry.
By the way, I got lucky.
I got lucky with sales.
But anybody right now, people go to become a doctor,
they spend seven years, right, in school,
pay back 250 grand in student loan debt,
then spend three more years in residency
making 60,000 a year after 10 years
to hopefully self-incorporate, open a practice,
make 500 grand a year.
Literally, you can get in sales
and you can make 500 grand in year one.
By the way, what does
it cost to get in sales?
Zero.
So a guy like me at 18 years old,
made bad grades, straight Ds in school.
Dad told me, get a job, stay out of jail.
The barrier of entry to sell was zero.
Made 125 grand my first year, 225 my second year,
third year I was 20 years old, made 500 grand.
Anyone, and I mean anyone, 95% of the population's lost.
They can get in sales and they can become
a multi-millionaire in the next five years.
A lot of people, they see these,
they see the multi-million dollar house,
they see the empire that you built,
but they don't realize, like, do you come from money?
Absolutely not.
By the way, anybody watching this right now,
broken people are the most dangerous.
If you're broke, it means this.
It's called bounce-ology.
I take a tennis ball, right,
and I freaking slam it on the ground.
From here to the ground is only this distance.
But so once it hits the ground,
it just fires back up super high.
So if you're broke and
you're lost, it's like rock bottom.
I was rock bottom for 18 years.
And at 19, when I found sales,
they say when the pain overrides the fear of change,
people change.
People that are comfortable don't
have a high level of pain,
so their change is never really big.
Broke people, a lot of them,
when you're sick and tired of being sick and tired,
and you're like, dude, I
ain't gonna be broke no more.
I'm not gonna be a loser no more.
This isn't gonna be my bloodline anymore.
Those people that are watching this,
which are really the masses, the people that you reach,
those people are dangerous.
And by the way, without a test, there's no testimony.
Do you wanna see some guy
and go follow him who came up this much,
or do you wanna find a
guy that came up this much?
That's my dude.
What is your secret to sales?
You've closed massive multimillion dollar deals
consistently throughout your entire life.
What is Andy Elliott's secret to sales?
I care more about my clients
than they care about themselves.
That's it, whoever cares most about the client wins.
Whether the client cares about themself
more than you care about them,
or whether I care about you
more than you care about yourself.
There's this thing called eyes.
Eyes are the window to the soul.
When I'm talking to you,
you can tell if you're the
most important thing to me or not.
And honestly, a lot of people,
they're not really where they're at.
So we're here together right now.
I've got a million other
things going on in my life.
I'm not thinking about one of them.
I'm thinking about you.
People don't do that anymore.
They're not really where they are.
So you gotta be where your feet are,
and then also you gotta understand this, okay?
The secret in sales is that
when I learned that sales was my way out
and it was gonna make me
rich if I was great at it,
they say if you treat something like it's the beginning,
there'll never be an end.
Dude, every time I sell, I'm so freaking jacked up.
It's like I just chew Viagra for sales.
Seriously, I'm excited.
I love it.
I never get exhausted.
It never gets burned out.
It never gets old to me.
I don't care how much money I make.
I don't care how big the deal is.
The next deal, I'm hungrier than that deal.
Whoever's the hungriest wins.
That's the game.
So the reason why I've never burned out
is because I am where my feet are.
I love my clients.
And by the way, what's
the good rule of the business
if you wanna dominate everybody?
Take care of your clients better
than they've ever been taken care of.
Do what I'm with people and make them feel better
than anybody's ever made them feel.
Remember, people don't always remember what you said,
but they'll always remember the way you made them feel.
Was all this worth it?
Hell yes, and I'm gonna tell you a lie.
I hear all these big influencers and entrepreneur,
they say that not everybody's built for this shit.
Bullshit.
Everybody's built for it.
If you can just believe in you
and no one else believes in you, that's enough.
Of course it's worth it.
Dude, listen, you're gonna die.
You're gonna die one day.
You wanna be remembered?
You wanna change anyone's life along the way?
Do you wanna do anything
that makes you feel good in your heart?
You wanna have the art of achievement
and the art of fulfillment?
Go psycho.
There's something that I say
that scares the shit out of people,
and I say, hey James,
have you ever thought about the unlived life?
This is the one that you were supposed to live.
This is the one when God made you,
he wanted you to live this life,
but you never had the courage to do it.
Is it worth it?
Is it worth it to get to the unlived life?
Yeah, bet your ass it is.
Either get there or die trying,
but damn sure don't be average.
Never conform, never become civilized, ever.
I love it.
That was phenomenal, man.
Thank you so much, man,
for letting us come out here.
That was amazing.
My guy Andy just dropped so much game
for everybody watching this video right now,
but I want you to like and subscribe
for amazing content we have coming very, very soon.
And I've got a very special announcement to make.
On June 4th, the Hard Knocks family
is launching something massive,
the biggest thing that we've ever built out
that's gonna enable you guys
to connect and learn from directly
the people that we interview in these videos
every single week.
This is the biggest thing on the internet,
and it's gonna be the biggest thing
for the entrepreneur community,
and it's in the description below.
So click the link in the description below
to join the wait list for
what we're launching on June 4th.
I promise you, you do not wanna miss it.
But we'll see you guys in the next video.
Click right up here to watch our full video
going all over Las Vegas asking multimillionaires
how you can start your path
to becoming financially free in 2024.
We'll see you in the next video.